No animals were harmed during
the filming of this series.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
Alps!
Brothers!
-Brothers!
We are here brothers!
-Hang on!
-Hang on, brothers!
We are here!
-My Alps!
-Brothers, make a sound!
-Come on!
My Bey!
My Bey, this won't open!
Brothers!
Hang on!
My Bey!
It is stuck, my Bey!
Alps!
-I won't let go!
-My Bey!
I won't leave my Alps!
-Alps!
-My Bey!
Alps!
There must be another way out!
-We will find it, my Bey.
-Come on!
-We will find it.
Come on, Alps!
-Here!
-Osman!
Your Alps are dead!
You will die too!
-Come on! Come on!
-Come on! Let's find a way out!
-Come on!
Alps!
Brothers!
Attack!
Allahu Akbar!
Brothers! Are you all right!
Brothers!
Gencebay! Take this, brother!
Come on!
Come on, Saltuk!
Let me help.
I'm here!
I am not dead!
Come on!
-Come on!
Come on! Let's go!
My Bey!
Brothers!
Come on, brothers!
Come on!
Brothers!
-Boran!
-My Bey!
Come here!
My Bey.
Some Alps couldn't make it.
There are many casualties.
Come on.
My brothers!
You bastard!
-Let me go! I won't come!
-Walk! Walk!
Don't make this harder!
You are forcing her! Let her go!
I made so many preparations.
I will marry Mari.
Don't you see!
Mari doesn't want you!
This should be between you and me.
Let her go, Kosses!
Don't hurt him!
Nikola!
All right, Nikola!
Please don't hurt him!
I wanted to run away. He just helped!
Please, brother! Please!
Nikola, please!
So he just helped?
I can't even recognize you anymore, Mari.
What did this man do to you!
How can you ask for help from our
enemy, Mari? How?
How could you, Kosses?
What kind of a brother are you to do this
to your sister?
But don't worry. Your time will come too.
I will ask you to account for every tear
you made her shed.
If I am Turgut Bey, I will be your executioner
and put you through hell!
Hell!
No, brother!
Don't! Please!
You...
...will be dead...
...today!
Your death will be...
...by our hands!
Dreams, dreams, Turgut Bey!
You've ruined the best day of my life.
I will kill you...
...in such a way that...
...it will be an example for all
my enemies.
-An example.
-Kill me.
Kill me!
Or I will make you regret it, Nikola!
Nikola!
All right! Let him go. If you let him go
without any harm...
...I promise I will marry you.
Don't do this, Mari!
-Don't do this.
-Shut up.
Don't say such things.
If I am alive, I won't let you go to this
tyrant.
Dear Mari.
You will marry me anyway.
Why would I let him go?
You bastard!
Enough.
Let's have some fun.
Get him up.
Stop! Nikola don't!
Nikola, please, don't!
- Brother, please help!
-Enough!
Enough!
Enough.
Let Mari go.
Tie him up!
Tie.
Tie me up, Nikola!
Do your best.
But know that...
...even if you marry Mari...
...she will never want you.
Take his clothes off too.
Look at this!
You don't grow in here but...
...I am sure there is a reason.
In the name of Allah.
Nikola! Don't!
Brother! Nikola don't!
Nikola.
I must get help.
I must go to the tribe at once.
Brother, please do something!
Boran!
Take him! Take him!
Retreat!
-Boran!
-Brother!
Boran!
My Bey!
My Bey, stop!
My Bey.
They are alive!
They are injured!
Brother!
-Brother.
I won't let them take you.
Look at these.
Tell me, Bala.
How do you feel?
Do you think it is a girl or a boy?
I don't know.
As long as it is healthy.
Mother, what do you think?
My mother has made many correct
guesses.
I don't know. I feel like it's a boy.
As long as it is healthy.
I hope.
Come in!
Kumral Abdal.
Turgut Bey and the Lord's sister
got caught by the Lord...
...as they were running away.
The situation is terrible, Selcen Hatun.
They will kill him.
What are you saying?
-Inform Gündüz immediately!
-Mother.
Gündüz is at Söğüt.
What will we do?
A Bey's Hatun is here, mother!
I won't let those heathens take Turgut
or Mari.
Aygül, get the Alps ready. We must hurry.
Don't worry, mother.
What about Turgut Bey's Alps?
There were none.
You find them, Kumral Abdal.
You know where they are.
-Mother.
-Protect yourselves, my girl.
Nikola, stop.
Nikola, stop!
He will pay, Mari!
He will!
Give it to me!
He won't die peacefully.
You won't die peacefully, Turgut.
No, Nikola!
Do you think these feet can walk?
Nikola! I am begging you!
Please, stop!
Give it to me!
Let them do what they want, Mari.
Please, don't beg these bastards.
You made a big mistake, Turgut.
A huge mistake!
Come on, cut my hand.
Then speak.
Or...
...aren't you man enough, Nikola?
I will cut your tongue, Turgut!
Then you won't speak and cross the line.
It's okay.
Look at me.
Let speaking to what's mine...
...if you even look at what's mine...
...I will carve out your eyes!
Do you understand?
I will carve them!
Look, Mari.
This is what you get when you make
the wrong decision.
Let me go! I hate you!
My dear wife Mari.
You always ask me why I don't
do what you desire.
Why I don't ask for your opinion.
Now I am asking. Should I...
...cut Turgut's tongue or carve out his
eyes?
I am not your wife!
I hate you!
-I hate you!
-Enough!
Nikola, stop!
Brothers.
May Allah be pleased with you, brother.
There is no one else inside, my Bey.
What is your order?
My Bey.
My brother's compass is here.
But he is taken by heathens.
We will take Boran from them...
...as we took their property.
All of their time will come.
All of them.
We'll make them pay for
both the captives and our martyrs.
Bay Sungur and the other Alps will not
let anyone...
...take a step in the mines except us.
We will go and...
...bury our martyrs.
Come on, Alps.
Turgut Bey's Alps were looking for him.
Aygül, come on.
Be careful.
Come on!
Let's go!
I will make you suffer every pain a person
can suffer.
Every pain!
No, Nikola!
Nikola, stop!
Mari?
What is it?
Do you feel sorry for this shepherd?
I will break every bone you have.
Brother, do something!
He will die!
This is enough.
Enough!
Let me go! Damn it!
Shut up, Mari!
Enough!
Mari...
This is the end.
The end of Turgut Bey.
-No!
-Yes.
-No, Nikola!
-Yes!
No, Nikola!
I am looking for the world.
Do you know where it is?
You smell like the world.
We were losing a lunatic. You came.
Now we are complete.
What do you want, lunatic?
The lovers don't die.
The lovers don't die!
I am here, Turgut Bey!
Mari!
Come on!
Turgut, come on!
No, no! Let go!
Come on!
Attack!
Here!
Mari, watch out!
Nikola!
Turgut!
Get out of my way!
You useless piece of--
Get out!
You are oppressed under the
reign of chaos.
You need order.
A strong head is needed
for that order.
I'm that head.
The Vizier of the Great Seljuks,
Alemşah!
These borders are now
under my rule.
Onur.
Is Lord Nikola informed of my arrival?
I sent a messenger, my vizier.
Lord Nikola awaits you.
I'll go to him first.
Then to Kayı Tribe.
I'll see the rebel named
Osman in his home.
Let's see who is this
famous Osman.
Osman or the lords, make no
difference.
They all will change their politics.
Now, the only truth on these lands...
is my word.
They all will learn this.
Slowly. Slowly.
Turgut Bey!
Mari!
Are you alright?
Malhun Hatun.
Aygül.
They came in time.
Thank you.
Son.
Your wounds are severe.
You need to go to the infirmary.
I will but...
Osman Bey...
any news from him?
Where is he?
My Allah protect him.
Cerkutay!
My Allah protect us!
My bey.
Cerkutay. Cerkutay, thank Allah!
You are here!
Thank Allah!
Osman?
Are you alright?
Turgut Bey.
You ask about me, Osman Bey.
I'm alright, thank Allah.
But you?
How?
The mine belongs to the Kayı now.
But we have martyrs.
My brother Boran...
is captured by Rogatus.
My bey.
The land becomes home when
it gets wet by blood.
What happened?
You are wounded.
You are wounded, Cerkutay!
We must go to the infirmary!
Alps! Prepare the infirmary!
It's nothing.
The sane leaves...
the insane stays.
Boran.
Boran is in the hands of
the heathens, Aygül.
İnegöl Castle
We'll kill you all!
All of you!
You gave the order, right, Rogatus?
We will kill you too.
Especially you!
Demon!
I'll have your head.
I'll have your head!
Even now, you are threatening
us.
Your wife was like that too.
She also stood tall.
She resisted.
But she died.
You will share the same fate.
Not only you, all the Turks!
We aren't afraid of death.
We can't drain away by dying.
I'll be a martyr and reach to my wife.
But I won't go anywhere
before killing you.
He will kill us.
Wait.
Take a breath.
No. No.
I'll keep you for Nikola.
He'll take his anger out on you.
Until then, enjoy being here.
Keep your eyes on him.
Do you know how your wife died?
Do you want me to tell you?
Demon!
The poison took her breath first.
-Silence!
-Then...
her veins exploded.
Shut up!
Do you know that pain?
It's more painful than...
you can ever imagine.
Silence!
She crawled...
while agonizing.
Shut your mouth up!
But she was tough.
At that condition...
she tried to be the hero.
And with a slice of a sword...
she died.
I swear that...
I won't die before making you feel
the pain you inflicted on Gonca.
Before taking your head off...
the ground is haram for me.
Haram!
Like it wasn't enough...
now we have his wife!
Damn it!
Where did they come from?
Damn them all!
All of them!
Damn them!
Where did they come from?
Where?
Damn them!
Lord Kosses' dear sister Mari.
How could you do this to me?
I'll lose my mind, Nikola!
We'll gather our armies at once!
Look, if it's Osman's wife who
took Mari...
only place they'll go is Kayı Tribe.
I'll destroy them.
All of them.
We'll burn it.
No one will survive. Not even
the buildings.
I'll burn Kayı Tribe, Kosses!
I will burn it!
Are you mad, Nikola? Will you burn
it when Mari is inside?
I'll never allow this!
I'll go alone to take Mari.
What do you mean alone?
What am I?
-She was going to be my wife!
-She will be, Nikola!
If you attack the tribe with your army,
it will be a mess.
It's best for you to return to
the castle and stay calm.
What are you saying, Kosses?
They'll teach what's mine...
and I'll stay at my castle?
You don't understand, Nikola. If you
attack, you'll lose Mari forever!
I'll bring you Mari.
I promise you.
Trust me.
Alright.
Go, Kosses.
Go and take Mari.
I'm going.
I hope you are right.
I hope you are right, Kosses.
I hope so.
Mari...
I'm not your wife!
I hate you!
Mari...
Bring me Mari.
Bring her...
so that I can choke her with
my own hands.
With my own hands.
My condolences, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
The iron in those mines...
it's wet with my martyrs' blood.
What shield can block the attacks...
of the swords made by that iron?
What wall can stand against the balls
made with those iron?
No wall, Kumral Abdal.
No wall.
I won't leave Boran to the heathens.
Then, it'll be time to attack
the walls.
Osman Bey, as long as...
these hands have power
to hold a sword...
I'll be with you.
Don't worry. We won't leave
Boran to the heathens.
May I enter, my bey?
Come.
My bey, Lord Kosses is here.
He wants audience.
Let him wait.
As you order, my bey.
He must be here to see his sister.
Are we keeping here by force that we can
give her when he asks?
I'm coming, Osman Bey.
I have things to say.
Turgut Bey, wait.
Your wounds are fresh.
Kumral Abdal will tend them.
Take some rest.
Let me, Osman Bey.
Let me.
Now, Mari is with us.
You think about the wedding date.
I'll convince Kosses.
But...
don't forget that...
our real goal is conquest.
Alright.
The conquests begins in the heart.
You conquered Mari's heart.
You saved her from the tyrants.
Move.
Give me your weapon first, Lord Kosses.
Look at me, nomad!
No one can take my sword away
from me today! Do you get it?
Move now!
Alps!
Let him come with his sword!
You are playing with fire, Osman!
Do you think your flames are strong
enough to burn me?
You are joining Turgut's beadledom!
My sister was kidnapped.
And it's your wife who did it!
I'm here to take her.
You will give her.
We didn't kidnap Mari.
And we aren't keeping her by force.
We saved her from tyrants.
Tyrants?
Osman.
She is my sister.
I will take her.
I will break every hand that tries
to touch my guests.
You can be sure of that.
Even if it's her brother.
My fire won't burn you.
It will be the emperor's.
If you don't change your decision.
I'll go to Constantinople personally
and return with the emperor's army.
Not only the emperor...
even if you return with the crusaders...
I will never give Mari to you.
Our laws never allow us to hand over
the refugees.
That law will be the end of you
and your tribe, Osman Bey.
Come on now.
Come to yourself.
What did I tell you?
Haven't I told you to marry you
to one of us when you first came here?
You found the bravest and strongest of
them.
Smile now.
I'm grateful to all of you.
If you didn't come...
Turgut would die.
Because of me.
My pretty daughter.
The bad days are in the past now.
Now, it's time to talk about
good things, my daughter.
I put you and your tribe in danger
by coming here.
Mari.
This is Kayı Tribe.
We never abandon those
who ask for our help.
If they come,
they will find.
They'll want to hurt you.
Both my brother and Nikola
won't let this slip.
Bala is right. We are comrades
in arms now.
Let them come.
Take rest now.
Don't think about this.
What if something happens to you?
May I enter, Malhun Hatun?
Come, Alaca.
Malhun Hatun, Lord Kosses is here.
He wants to see Mari.
Shh, my girl. Be at ease.
This is Kayı Tribe.
As long as you don't want it, Osman Bey
won't let anyone...
take you.
I just lost my warriors.
I didn't even bury them yet.
Your dear friend Rogatus...
is keeping one of my alps
as a hostage.
My wrath is like great mountains!
Now, tell me!
Which one is scarier, the fire of
the cross or my fury?
Turgut went beyond his limit
for the second time.
You know it too!
He deceived Mari!
You can't keep her here by force!
No one is keeping me here
by force! I stay with my free will.
I won't return, brother.
Mari.
Please, don't force me.
Let's leave here nicely.
Never.
I'll never come with you.
You should've known that I wouldn't
stay where I'm ignored.
If you don't come with me now,
I'll return with a great army.
You will return with an army
to get your sister's corpse?
Don't hold back. If you want
me to kill myself...
do it.
When you don't find what you want...
you show your teeth.
You come to my tribe and threaten
me with an army!
If you have the courage...
do it.
Do it and see what happens!
But I'll never give you Mari.
-Osman...
-If you have nothing to say...
leave now.
As you wish, Mari.
As you wish.
Osman took the mine, Nikola.
How did they get out of that
mine alive?
Won't anything go in order today?
How did it happen, Rogatus?
Why does it matter?
He took it.
But we took something he
values dearly.
What?
In return of the mine,
we took his most loyal alp.
Boran.
Finally. Finally!
Finally, good news!
Osman loves his alps so much!
What about Kosses?
Where is he?
He went to take Mari.
From Osman.
-May I enter.
-Come.
You shouldn't be on your feet.
May I?
It was a tough day for you too.
I wanted to know if you
are alright.
They hurt you because of me.
I was so afraid that something
would happen to you.
If something had happened to you...
I would never forgive myself.
Don't cry.
Your pretty eyes shouldn't
be wet.
Your tears hurt me much
more than...
what they've done.
Don't cry.
Now.
When I saw this at the market...
it reminded me of you.
I thought...
I thought I could buy it
for you.
Today is the day, it seems.
It's so beautiful.
And so are you.
I'm grateful.
Mari.
I don't know what to say.
You...
did you ever think about it?
Being...
-May I enter?
-Come.
Osman Bey awaits you at his tent.
Let's go then.
You were saying something.
Let's go.
İnegöl Castle
You couldn't get Mari.
Is that so?
You are making no sense, Nikola.
What are you doing?
You ruined my reputation!
Mari was kidnapped because
of you!
You couldn't control a woman!
The one you call a woman
is my sister, Nikola!
So, stop aiming at me
with your anger!
I won'T!
Enough!
We took an oath!
We'll stay united!
We won't go after each other!
Have you forgotten about it?
We were going to grow together!
We will!
If you manage to stay calm!
Isn't that so, Rogatus?
We need to sit as gentlemen and
talk about how we'll take Mari back.
You put us into this situation!
-Is that so?
-I'll take us out!
How?
Father, son, the holy spirit.
Christ will show us the way.
Holy God!
Did Rogatus turn you religious, Nikola?
No! No!
It's what I've experienced.
Someone is coming...
to help us.
Who?
The Vizier of the Seljuks...
Vizier Alemşah!
Vizier Alemşah.
Welcome.
I greet the strong lords of these lands.
But I see that you don't rule according
to your power.
There is still chaos in your lands.
Stability requires order.
This order is lost, Nikola.
You know who broke it better
than us, Vizier Alemşah.
How will we take Boran, Osman Bey?
In the tyrant's hands,
in a dungeon...
I know what they are doing
to him now.
How will we save Boran?
What happens if he is in a dungeon?
We'll be face to face with our Allah.
A dungeon is seclusion for us.
Let's say they banish us
to heathen lands...
banish is hejira for us!
Let's say they killed Boran...
death is shada for us!
It's martyrdom!
But...
we won't leave anyone behind.
We'll take my brother Boran
from them.
And we'll look forward.
With the name of Allah.
Go on.
Enjoy it.
My daughter, why aren't
you eating?
My brother's threats.
I'm afraid that he'll do something,
Selcan Hatun.
You don't seem affected.
We took these lands with
our blood...
with our weapons.
We wanted justice to reign
in our lands.
Mercy to reign on our lands.
If we were to give you because
of the emperor...
as our ancestors say...
If cruelty enters from a window...
laws leave from the door.
We are talking about the emperor's
army, Osman Bey.
I know your tribe, Turgut Bey's
tribe.
How can you stand?
Even if your brother marches on us
with a great army, as he said...
he can't establish superiority
against us.
Do you think this is all of us?
Dodurga, Yazır, Eymür, Salur...
Bayat and Avşar.
From Kastamonu to Dengizli,
all tribes...
if an army had marched against us,
we'd turn into one strong fist.
Do you know what a river is, my girl?
Have you ever seen one?
Do you know what a sea is?
I do.
When I was in Constantinople,
I would go the shore...
and watch the sea for hours.
Here.
As all those rivers have one
source...
so do we.
As those rivers unite
in the sea...
we unite under the
flag of Islam.
Just like that.
We have friendly hearts
from all cities...
that we love,
and that love us.
For those friendly hearts,
many battles can be fought.
Many suffering can be endured.
Many roads can be traveled.
If Allah destines it...
soon we'll go to Konya...
for a friend of us.
When we reach Konya...
I'll visit Sultan Mesut too.
As you wish, my sheik.
Send my regard to the friends and
to Sultan Mesut.
Alright.
But...
you should be at ease.
As long as you don't want it,
no one can take you from here.
Your courage, determination;
it's truly impressive.
Now, Seljuks are here, lords.
Now, tell me.
For what do you need
my help?
My sister.
Vizier Alemşah.
And...
my future wife.
True. She is in Osman's
tribe.
They are keeping her there
by force.
And if I can't take her nicely...
I'll personally go to Constantinople...
and ask for an army
from the emperor.
That's not needed, Kosses.
I'm telling you that I'll
form order here.
There is no need to disturb
Emperor Andronikus...
for such a small problem.
I'll take care of it.
Osman's alp, Boran.
I heard that you keep him, Nikola.
Vizier Alemşah.
Where did you hear this from?
Nikola.
I know the tree that drops leaves
early...
the river that floods late...
and everything that's
happening in these lands.
Boran.
What do you plan to do with him?
Gonca?
Boran.
Lay, Boran.
Lay down.
Rest.
You are here, huh?
You are next to me?
I am.
It's too cold, Gonca.
Too cold.
Look at this alp of Kayı!
What can cold do to my valiant?
I missed you so much.
It pains my heart.
Please, speak a little more.
A little more.
I'm always cold in your absence.
Your longing is too hard.
It's not like any other pain.
It doesn't go.
Don't grow the longing...
but the reunion, my valiant.
Grow the reunion.
Gonca.
Don't leave me.
When the time comes...
I will leave too.
May that time never come, Gonca.
Don't go, Gonca.
I beg you, don't.
Don't leave, Gonca.
Don't.
I told you, Boran.
This isn't the end.
In the afterlife...
we'll meet for sure.
Don't go, Gonca!
I beg you, don't leave.
Gonca, stay.
Don't go, Gonca.
You took my sun away.
I won't die before taking your head.
I won't die.
Laugh.
I'll tie him at the square of İnegöl.
He'll starve.
He'll be thirsty.
And the people will lose their
sleeps for a while, because...
they'll listen to him agonizing.
I'll make him an example.
I've had the drums played all day.
All the people will witness the death
of Osman's most loyal man.
Good.
But I have a better plan.
Hera?
What are you doing here?
We heard it.
Your soldiers were killed.
I thought something happened to you.
Thank God you are alright.
My father.
My father wanted me to convey an
important information to Osman Bey.
Alright.
Then go...
and tell my bey.
Alright.
May I enter, my bey.
Come in.
My bey, I went after Rogatus
by your order.
He went to İnegöl,
not to his castle.
He is after some other treachery.
What else?
My bey, criers were wandering
on the square of İnegöl.
Tell me.
Boran Alp...
will be killed at the square
tomorrow.
What are you saying?
A Turkish soldier...
falls on the battlefield.
Not on a city square!
Tell all the alps!
It's Osman Bey's order!
We are going to İnegöl!
As you order, my bey.
May I enter, my bey.
Come.
Welcome, Hera.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Are you only here to convey
your father's words?
Aren't you sad about the passing
of my soldiers?
Of course, Osman Bey.
Alright, then.
Don't be sad any longer.
We need your help.
Of course.
Of course, whatever you need.
It's good that you are here.
We'll save Boran thanks to you.
Saltuk said it.
You didn't eat anything.
Come on, Cerkutay. Eat.
I don't want it, Aygül Hatun.
Thank you.
When does Cerkutay ever not
want food?
Come on. Eat a little.
My brother is captured
by the heathens.
How can Cerkutay eat?
Who knows what they are doing
to my brother.
They are torturing Boran.
Cerkutay.
Don't do this.
You said that Cerkutay is a mountain...
no tornado can break it down.
Now, you should stand like a mountain.
I believe in you.
You will get your revenge.
And you'll bring our brother
Boran safe and sound.
I will, huh?
Yes, you will.
Come on.
Don't let it get cold.
Cerkutay.
Boran is in the hands of the heathens.
It's not the time but...
I thought a lot, Cerkutay.
Ever since Gonca left us, I've
been thinking.
And the things that happened
today.
You might not have survived
that mine.
When I saw the martyrs
entering the tribe...
I was so afraid.
Death...
is so close.
Maybe...
maybe it's as far away.
What are you saying, mad girl?
The world...
the world doesn't last long.
You asked me a question.
What question--
When did I ask it?
Let's not wait.
What?
Let's marry, Cerkutay!
Are you serious, mad girl?
I am serious...
mad boy.
The secret is revealed.
The lovers are united.
The secret of love is patience.
You revealed the truth, my valiant.
May the peace, mercy, and blessings
of Allah be with you.
of Allah be with you
O' my Allah!
You are the judge!
Your wisdom is over anything.
You are the owner!
You own all there is!
When...
we shoot an arrow...
we know that it's not us who
shoots it.
It's your blessing.
We know that...
you broke the plans of those
who deny you.
Destine us to be grateful
for that, my Allah.
My Allah...
give us strenght to...
spread your names to all
over the earth.
Destine us to avenge...
our brother who fell martyrs...
our alps who fell martyrs...
on this holy goal.
My Allah...
destine us to...
save my brother Boran...
from the hands of the heathens.
Amin, my Allah.
Amin.
Alps!
We are going to save our brother.
My bey, Seljuk Vizier Alemşah is coming.
Welcome! Welcome!
Welcome, my vizier!
Welcome to the Kayı lands,
Vizier Alemşah.
His eyes look evil.
Kayı is the tree that bears
fruits...
and he is here to stone it.
Mother, he just arrived.
Why are you saying that?
His gaze reminded me of Sadettin Köpek.
He has the same treachery.
I'm a judge of character, my girl.
I can tell who is a warrior and
who is a traitor.
Osman Bey, I'm here to close another era.
It's end of the era that you acted
as you wanted.
Complete your sentence, vizier.
You forbid Turkmen tribes to trade
with the lords.
And then you made a deal
with the İznik's governor.
Whose permission did you get?
Whose permission is needed
for doing best for the Turkmens?
Of Konya, Osman Bey.
Of Konya.
Is there a free state in Konya
that I can take permission.
Know your place!
Taking mines, raiding places
as you want!
What's your goal, Osman Bey?
And you are questioning the
sovereinity of the state!
The weapons that you will make...
how do we know that they won't
be pointed at the Seljuks?
Know your words!
I respect your position!
But know your place.
What you talk about is treason.
I never betray!
It's the order of Sultan Mesud.
For the trade and
actions you took on your own...
without a permission...
the taxation of the Kayı Tribe
is doubled.
The state is here now.
Give me a room in Söğüt.
From now, I'll be stationed here.
It'll be as you say.
Onur, I want the Turkmen beys
at the inn.
I'll talk to them.
I want you and Turgut Bey there,
and ready.
We'll come.
If you don't have anything else to say.
If you allow me...
I have important things to do.
Take care of your last jobs, Osman Bey.
From now, I'll determine
what's important for you.
When the people is mourning for
the martyrs, he doubled the taxes.
We'll find a way, brother.
But...
we'll save Boran first.
The door.
These wounds are scabbed.
No.
Do you know what I'll do to you?
I'll tear you into pieces.
And send your pieces...
to your beloved Osman!
Craven dog!
Don't worry. I won't do it right away.
I'll corner Osman first.
Having an alp like you imprisoned by
me must've driven him crazy!
Yes.
Now, he is ready to do anything.
Anything!
Just what I want!
Allahu Akbar!
Heathen!
Kill me now when you
have the chance.
Otherwise, sooner or later...
I'll take your life.
Turks!
And your empty courage!
Empty!
Come!
Let's see if you'll keep your
courage when you are crucified.
Alps!
As we talked, our warriors entered
İnegöl earlier.
They'll gather information there.
But...
they don't even have weapons.
For this reason, we'll enter from
the front gates on Hera Hatun's cart.
The weapons will be on the cart.
After we enter the city,
you'll give the alps their weapons.
The rest depends on our
efforts.
We'll save our brother Boran.
May Allah bless our efforts.
As you order, my bey.
Come on.
İnegöl Castle
Sacred children of Byzantium!
The Turk you see here...
is the most loyal alp of Osman,
Boran Alp!
What did our archenemy Osman
do to us?
He took our village!
He took our mine!
He killed our people!
He killed you!
And he'll continue to do so!
So...
when Osman took our village...
took our mines...
killed you...
where was Boran Alp?
He was with Osman!
I will kill you.
What will happen now?
To make an example...
he'll be bait for birds and
animals!
Yes, he should be!
Then, it will be Osman's turn!
Yes, Lord Nikola!
He is here now.
We will do...
whatever you want!
He is yours.
My Allah!
My powerful Allah!
I am not going to bow down...
...even if they murder me right now.
Our prophet didn't bow down
to any difficulty.
I won't too!
If I become a martyr here...
I am going to witness...
...the vastidity of....
...our prophet, Allah's blessings
and peace be with him.
Allahu Akbar
(Allah is the greatest!)
Where do the martyrs go?
To heaven.
Gonca Hatun, Alps, all of them
are in heaven.
Kayı's valiant alps!
What are you doing?
We are thinking of our martyrs,
Kumral Abdal.
You can answer us.
Do all the martyrs go the same place?
In Quran, it is said that...
"Never say that those martyred
in the cause of Allah are dead—
in fact, they are alive!
...But you do not perceive it."
Martyrs don't die.
We are going to Bedr, sons!
Here he is!
Coming as he does!
He is fearless!
Every step of him fears the enemy!
Look at him!
He beats whoever crosses his way!
Allah Allah!
Every sword wound that the lying infidels
have is made by him!
Who is that?
Do you know?
The master of martyrs!
Allah's lion Hamza!
Mushriks wants to take revenge.
Utbe's daughter Hint...
...assigns her slave Zenci to...
... take revenge for
her uncle and father.
She assigns her slave Wahshi...
...to take revenge for her uncle and father.
It's dusty everywhere!
Where is here?
This is Uhud.
My heart burns!
Uhud means tear!
The war started.
The Holy knows it all!
He had a dream of this!
Look!
There he is!
He has no shield!
He beats everyone in front of him
with his double sword!
The master of martyrs fights!
Mushriks are afraid of him!
Allah Allah!
Oh my...
There is someone.
He has a spear.
Wahshi
Don't do it, Wahshi.
Don't, don't!
Don't do it!
You'll regret!
Don't do it Wahshi!
He hid behind a rock,
watching for an oppotunity.
He rises his spear...
...throws it...
He shot!
He threw the spear!
He did it!
My Hamza is down.
Uhud bleeds.
Hadrat Hamza is down.
Hint stands over his head.
Don't!
My Hamza is gone!
He is gone!
The secret is revealed!
My Hamza became a martyr.
How could they do this?
Greatly named like himself,
Mohammed is crying.
The secret is revealed, valiants!
My Hamza became a martyr.
They are not dead.
Don't call them dead.
Martyrs don't die.
You cannot call the martyrs dead.
- Martyrs don't die!
Gonca Hatun and alps became martyr but...
We are still here!
We'll carry the banner of Kayi!
We will!
Praise be to our Allah, valiants!
Praise be to our Allah!
Stop!
What did you come for?
I am asking you, dumb!
We are coming from Nikea to shop
with my wife.
Where you are coming from doesn't matter.
Get off.
We'll search.
Search the carriage!
How dare you!
Searching the carriage of
Lord Saguros' daughter?
How dare you?
Sorry.
We misbehaved.
Open the way.
Or you'll pay dearly.
Soldiers!
Open the gates!
Let's go.
Gence Bey, get Alps ready.
I had a good Sogut tour.
The town planning impressed me.
Osman Bey is the hope for this land.
You are the light of Oghuz.
I expected a more thriving scene here.
I am sorry to say that...
...I couldn't find what
I imagined in Sogut.
It has many missings.
There is always
missings where human live.
But...
...the perfect ones see the whole.
The unperfect sees only the missings...
...in world.
You are absolutely right about
what you say, sheik Edebali.
However, seeing is not enough.
Our state wants Sogut to
have everything...
...that our state is short of.
Your breath shall enlight our way.
We want to walk together.
As long as our Allah lets us live...
...we walk in his way.
We like what He likes.
We stay away from what He dislikes.
We shall leave now.
We are going to see each other again.
If Allah permits...
...of course we will.
With that said...
We were about to leave as well.
We'll mention your arrival in Konya.
Vizier Alam Shah.
I would appreciate it.
Why are you going to Konya?
We are going to see a friend's face.
I am going to stay here.
We'll see each other when you return.
Go safely.
Eyvallah (Thanks).
My Sheik.
Do you have something in your mind?
Not particularly a friend visit but...
...we have to see Sultan Mesut.
As you command, my sheik.
He beat off every words of mine!
He chose his side a long time ago.
Go to Kosses.
Tell him to stop Edebali in Konya way.
Edebali shouldn't go to Konya, Konur!
Sultan Mesut should not know
what we are doing.
Brother!
Alps, trap!
Trap!
Osman Bey!
Ingoble dog!
Why would you kill Boran?
Is your aim to kill the pray...
...or to catch Osman who
will do everything to save him?
Vizier Alam Shah!
You want Osman dead too!
Turks don't run short of valiants, Nicola!
So we can sacrifice the rebel ones.
Captivate him, kill him,
whatever you want.
This is your decision.
What about Boran?
When Osman comes to save Boran...
there will be someone
else in place of him.
And you'll trap him with your soldiers.
Vizier Alam Shah.
I am glad to have common objectives.
I'll trap Osman.
Can I come in?
Come.
Welcome.
You are hurt.
You are lucky to have me here.
You are alive and in front of me
thanks to me.
If your fate was up to Osman Bey...
...we would be having your funeral now.
Hello, Edebali!
Where are you going without my permission?
The creator of this way and
our body is Allah.
If He wants us to go,
even the whole world cannot stop us.
If He doesn't want us to go...
...even all the ways are opened,
we can't arrive.
Is that so?
Let's ask Him.
No.
Your God doesn't want you to go today.
Soldier!
Attack!
My Sheik!
Soldier!
When the dog barks relying on
the number of them...
...the wolf choke them!
You outnumber us...
...but we are Turks!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com